解决方法是我们需要调用
The solution is that we need to call
Fragment.setHasOptionsMenu(true)。做完这步之后，我们将
Fragment.setHasOptionsMenu(true). That way, we'll
在 Fragment 中获得合适的菜单回调方法
get appropriate options menu callback
以至于我们能够
methods in the fragment, so that we can
inflate 菜单，以及当一个菜单项
inflate the menu and for when a menu item
被选择时的事件。这是inflate菜单的fragment。
is selected. And this is where the fragment
记得在 ForecaseFragment 类中，
inflates the menu. Remember from before that in the
我们有一个公开的空构造函数，并且
ForecastFragment class, we have a public empty constructor, and
我们也重写了 onCreateView。我们也在这定义了 fetchWeatherTask。
we also override onCreateView? We also define fetchWeatherTask here.
现在，我们正在重写一个另外的fragment的
Now, we're going to overide an additional fragment life
生命周期方法 onCreate。这是fragment被创建的地方。
cycle method called onCreate. This is where the fragment
这个方法在 onCreateView 方法之前执行，
is created, and this happens before the onCreate view
也就是在 UI 被初始化之前执行。因此，
method, which is where the UI gets initialized. So, in
在onCreate中，我们调用setHasOptionsMenu并设为true是为了
onCreate, we're going to call setHasOptionsMenu to be true to
表示我们想回调这些方法。
indicate that we want call backs for these methods.
当onCreateOptionsMenu被调用时，我们将inflate我们之前定义的菜单布局
When onCreateOptionsMenu is called, we're going to inflate the menu
叫做 forecasefragment。我们也将
layout that we defined earlier called forecast fragment. We'll also
得到通知当一个菜单项被选择时。当一个
get notified when a menu item is selected. When a menu item with
ID为actionrefresh的菜单项被调用时，我们将返回true。
ID action refresh is called, we're going to
在稍后的课程中，我们将更加细致地复习
return true for now. We're going to go
activity和fragment的生命周期方法。
over the activity and fragment life cycle methods in more detail in later
但是如果你想的话，你现在就可以读下面的链接文档。
lessons, but if you want, you can read the documentation linked below for now.